(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T06:32:31.666901",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は、 hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by ヴァイスシュヴァルツ Day2にご来場いただきまして、
Thank you very much for visiting
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish supported by Weiss Schwarz today.
誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ご来場のお客さまにお願いがございます。
We have a request for all visitors upon entry.
新型コロナウイルス感染拡大防止対策として、
As a COVID-19 infection prevention measure,
マスクの着用、手指の消毒、
please wear a mask, disinfect your hands,
ソーシャルディスタンスのご協力を お願いしております。
and cooperate with social distancing.
お並びいただく際やロビー内でも、
Please avoid eating and drinking in queues or lobbies.
お客さま同士の距離間を保っていただくよう ご協力をお願いいたします。
We also ask for your cooperation in maintaining distance.
暇つぶしのため、 立ち話などは お控えいただきますよう お願いいたします。
To prevent overcrowding, please refrain from gathering with others.
入場時に検温にて体温確認をさせていただいておりますが、
Body temperature checks are conducted at the entrance.
万が一、体調に異変を感じた場合は無理をせずスタッフへお声がけください。
If you feel unwell, please notify the staff without pushing yourself.
客席内での携帯電話はスマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
Please refrain from using smartphones inside your seat.
スマートフォンは新型コロナウイルス接触確認アプリCOCOAを使用するため、電源は切らずに、開園までにマナーモードに設定して おしまいください。
Smartphones should be set to Manner Mode without turning off power,
to allow the COCOA app to function.
また、携帯電話などにより撮影、録音、 録画は固くお断りいたします。
Also, please refrain from taking photos, recording videos, or audio on smartphones.
万が一発見した場合は、 データ削除の上、退場していただく場合がございます。
If you discover any violations, please delete the data and leave.
客席内での、もし、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為、
If you engage in dangerous behavior like diving or jumping,
ルールに反したコンサートライトの使用は禁止となります。
or use concert lights violating rules, they will be prohibited.
上記のことが守れない場合は、 公演を一時中断 もしくは中止させていただく可能性があります。
If you cannot follow these rules, performances may be suspended or canceled.
また、本公演では、 既定の前に立ち ご観覧いただくことを許可しております。
Also, in this performance, leaving your seat before leaving is permitted.
このほか、本公演では、避難誘導等の消化を行います。
Additionally, an evacuation drill will be conducted during this performance.
万が一避難が必要になった場合は、 すぐに非譲渡を転換しますので、仮の指示に従っていただきますようお願いいたします。
If evacuation is necessary, please follow staff instructions immediately.
公演終了後は、 避難防止 また、 ソーシャルディスタンス確保のため ブロックごとの規定対象にご協力のほど よろしくお願いいたします。
After the performance, please wait in your seat until instructed to exit in blocks.
スタッフの指示があるまでご自分の席でお待ちください。
Please wait in your seat until instructed by staff.
最後に、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、 お客さまの様子が映り込む可能性がございます。
Finally, streaming and recording cameras may enter the venue during this performance.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご容赦ください。
These images or photos may be used in promotions, so please understand in advance.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment until the doors open.
新型コロナウイルス感染拡大防止対策として、
As a COVID-19 infection prevention measure,
マスクの着用、手指の消毒、
please wear a mask, disinfect your hands,
ソーシャルディスタンスのご協力を お願いしております。
and cooperate with social distancing.
お並びいただく際やロビー内でも、
Please avoid eating and drinking in queues or lobbies.
お客さま同士の距離間を保っていただくよう ご協力をお願いいたします。
We also ask for your cooperation in maintaining distance.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 PENLIGHT COLORS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Tote Bag & Windbreaker]
[Official Items - Tapestry & Cushions]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
[Special Limited Items - Collaboration Cap & Pens]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Random Can Badges]
[Official Items - Acrylic Keyholders]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Acrylic Diorama & Clear Files]
[Official Items - Playing Cards & Pamphlet]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
[Special Limited Items - Coach Jacket & Sweatshirt]
[Special Limited Items - Logo T-Shirts]
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attendee Guidelines - Masks, Manner Mode, No Recording]
[Attendee Guidelines - No Cheering, Standing Rules]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 / ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
[Weiss Schwarz Premium Booster & Cards]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Card Stands & Binders]
[Official Items - Trading Badge Packs]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Plate Acrylic Stands & Tapestry]
[Official Items - Durable Stickers]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items - Can Badges & Hand Towels]
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attendee Guidelines]
Attention: To All Visitors
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも、止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Even in the hololive production booster pack,
Weiß Schwarz never stops!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション
Booster Pack: hololive production
好評発売中！
Now On Sale!
ブシロード
BUSHIROAD
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We're Chugai Mining's Content Department,
huge anime fans!
もっともっと！アニメを楽しみたい！
Want to enjoy anime more and more!
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発して、インターネットで販売しています！
With that passion, we plan, develop, and sell
anime merch online!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます！
We also run anime-collaborated cafés!
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check Twitter for the latest info!
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To All Visitors
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please refrain from cheering aloud
during the performance.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
[Plate Acrylic Stand / B2 Tapestry]
耐水シール
[Waterproof Stickers]
缶＆ハンドタオル
[Can Badge & Hand Towel Sets]
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attention: To All Visitors]
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 2
ペンライト / Tシャツ / マフラータオル
[Penlight / T-Shirts / Muffler Towel]
PENLIGHT COLORS
トートバッグ / サコッシュ / ウィンドブレーカー
[Tote Bag / Sacoche / Windbreaker]
ロゴクッション / ラバーバンド / タペストリー
[Logo Cushion / Rubber Band / Tapestry]
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
ランダム缶バッジ
[Random Can Badges]
アクリルキーホルダー
[Acrylic Keyholders]
クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
[Clear File Set / Acrylic Diorama]
トランプ 2022 / パンフレット
[Playing Cards 2022 / Pamphlet]
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS / MANGART BEAMS
[Special Limited Items: Mangart Beams]
hololive Logo S/S t-shirts / hololive SSS L/S t-shirts
[hololive Logo S/S T-Shirts / SSS L/S T-Shirts]
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attention: To All Visitors]
[Attention: Notice to Visitors]
公演中の注意事項
[Performance Guidelines]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 Official Items]
ブシロードアクリルカードスタンド / ブシロードカードバインダー
[Acrylic Card Stands & Card Binders]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items: Trading Badges]
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
[Plate Acrylic Stands & B2 Tapestries]
耐水シール 全31種
[Waterproof Stickers (31 Types)]
缶＆ハンドタオル 全9種
[Can Badge & Hand Towel Sets]
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
[Attention: Notice to Visitors]
公演中の注意事項
[Performance Guidelines]
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 2
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
[Official Items: Penlights & Apparel]
PENLIGHT COLORS
[Penlight Color Guide]
トートバッグ2022 / ウィンドブレーカー
[Tote Bags & Windbreakers]
ロゴクッション2022 / タペストリー
[Logo Cushions & Tapestries]
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
ランダム缶バッジ / ホロスターズ ランダム缶バッジ
[Random Can Badges]
アクリルキーホルダー
[Acrylic Keyholders]
クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
[Clear File Sets & Acrylic Dioramas]
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz, unstoppable even in the Hololive Production booster pack!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション 好評発売中！
Booster Pack Hololive Production is now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We are Chugai Mining's content department, big fans of anime!
アニメを楽しみたい！
We want to enjoy anime!
アニメグッズを企画開発してインターネットで販売しています！
We plan, develop, and sell anime merchandise online!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます
We also run anime collaboration cafes!
最新情報はTwitterで！
Get the latest info on Twitter!
ホロライブ6期生の沙花叉クロヱです。
I am Chloe Sakamata of Hololive 6th Generation.
本日は、ホロライブ3rdフェス「Link Your Wish」Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ DAY 2にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to Hololive 3rd Fes "Link Your Wish" Supported By Weiß Schwarz Day 2 today.
同じくホロライブ6期生の風真いろはでござる。今日は私たちが入場アナウンスを担当いたします。今日1日よろしくお願いいたします！
Likewise, I am Kazama Iroha of Hololive 6th Generation, and today we will be handling the venue announcements. We look forward to working with you today!
開演の前に、お客さまにご案内がございます。
Before the concert, we have some announcements for our audience.
まず初めに、会場の皆さまへめのご案内です。ロビー、客席内ではマスク着用が必須となります。公演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点からご遠慮ください。
First, we would like to inform everyone entering the venue that wearing a mask is mandatory in the lobby and seating areas, and any shouting during performances must be avoided to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
ぜひ拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いします。
Please show your support with applause and penlights instead!
また、会場内では立って応援いただいても問題ございませんが、周りのお客さまのご迷惑にならないようご配慮をお願いいたします。
Also, while standing to cheer inside the venue is permitted, please be mindful not to cause a nuisance to surrounding guests.
続いて、配信をご覧の皆さまへのご案内です。本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Next, a notice for everyone watching the stream: recording, filming, mirroring, or illegal uploading of this live broadcast is strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットで撮影をしていただくことやSNSで感想をつぶやいていただくことは大歓迎なので、皆さんハッシュタグ「#つながるホロライブDAY2」で感想をつぶやいて、SNSもいーっぱい盛り上げてください！
However, taking screenshots and sharing your impressions on social media is very welcome, so please share your thoughts widely using the hashtag #LinkYourWish_Day2!
本ライブ配信はデータ通信量が多くなることが想定されるため、スマートフォンでご覧になる場合はWi-Fiのご利用を推奨いたします。インターネット回線の接続が不安定な場合は、配信動画のクオリティを保証できませんのでご容赦ください。
Since live broadcasts may experience high data traffic, please use Wi-Fi on smartphones; if your connection is unstable, we cannot guarantee stream quality.
また、万全の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、生配信である性質上、不慮の障害で一時停止や映像の乱れなどが起こる可能性がありますことをあらかじめご容赦ください。
Also, while we prepare meticulously, live streams may occasionally encounter temporary interruptions or video glitches due to the nature of live broadcasts, so please understand in advance.
それでは、開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Now, please look forward to the concert starting soon!
Hello everyone, I am Kronii from Hololive English Council.
Hello everyone, I am Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Council.
And I'm Mumei from Hololive English Council. Thank you to everyone who came to today's Hololive 3rd Fes. Link Your Wish Supported by Weiß Schwarz Day 2. And I'm Baelz, also from Hololive English Council. Today, we will be in charge of all the announcements within the venue.
And I am Hakos Baelz, also from Hololive English Council. Today, we will be in charge of all the announcements within the venue.
We hope you have an amazing time!
Before we start the show, we have some quick announcements. We would like to first address the audience here today. Masks are mandatory and must be worn in the lobby and audience seats. Please refrain from shouting during the performances in order to prevent the spread of coronavirus.
Before we start the show, we have some quick announcements. We would like to first address the audience here today. Masks are mandatory and must be worn in the lobby and audience seats. Please refrain from shouting during the performances...
...in order to prevent the spread of coronavirus. We would love it if you support this with your hands and penlights. In addition, it is fine to stand up and cheer within the venue. However, please be considerate of those around you when doing so.
Next is a short reminder to all of you who will be watching the livestream. It is strictly prohibited to record, tape, mirror, or illegally upload this live performance.
However, you are definitely welcome to take pictures and share your experience on all social media platforms.
If you decide to do so, please use the hashtag #つながるホロライブDAY2 and feel free to share your thoughts on social media.
If you decide to do so, please use the hashtag #LinkYourWish_Day2 and feel free to share your thoughts on social media.
This live performance is expected to require a large amount of data transmission and bandwidth. We heavily recommend that you use Wi-Fi when viewing this event on your smartphones.
If your internet connection is unstable, we cannot guarantee the quality of the delivered video.
Although we will do our best to prepare for the live broadcasting, please keep in mind that due to the nature of live broadcasts, there is a possibility of pauses or disruptions in the video due to unforeseen problems.
We would like to ask you to please wait just a little longer for the show to start.
Halo semua, namaku Anya dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
Hello everyone, my name is Anya from Hololive Indonesia Generation 2.
Namaku Reine dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
My name is Reine from Hololive Indonesia Generation 2.
Terima kasih telah datang ke Hololive 3rd Fes Link Your Wish supported by Weiß Schwarz Day 2.
Thank you for coming to Hololive 3rd Fes "Link Your Wish" Supported by Weiß Schwarz Day 2.
Dan aku Ollie dari Hololive Indonesia Generasi 2. Hari ini, kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk membacakan pengumuman.
And I'm Ollie from Hololive Indonesia Generation 2. Today, we will be responsible for reading the announcements.
Semoga hari ini akan menjadi hari yang menyenangkan. Pertama-tama, ada beberapa pengumuman untuk para tamu...
Hopefully, today will be a very joyful day! First of all, there are some announcements for our guests...
Kepada para tamu, kami mohon untuk
To our guests, we kindly ask
selalu memakai masker saat berada di lobi maupun tempat duduk.
that you always wear a mask in the lobby or seating area.
Kami mohon juga untuk tidak mengeluarkan suara
We also ask you not to make noise
pada saat konser untuk mencegah penyebaran virus korona.
during the concert to prevent the spread of coronavirus.
Tolong dukung kami dengan tepukan tangan dan penlight.
Please support us with applause and penlights.
Anda diperbolehkan untuk mendukung sambil berdiri,
You are allowed to support while standing,
namun harap berhati-hati agar tidak merepotkan tamu lain.
but please be careful not to inconvenience other guests.
Selanjutnya adalah pengumuman
Next is an announcement
untuk para pendatang yang menonton livestream.
for attendees watching the livestream.
Anda dilarang untuk merekam, menayangkan,
You are prohibited from recording, broadcasting,
atau mengupload ulang stream konser secara ilegal.
or illegally re-uploading the concert stream.
Tapi sebagai gantinya, Anda dianjurkan
Instead, you are encouraged
untuk upload screenshot dan posting mengenai konser kami di media sosial.
to upload screenshots and post about our concert on social media.
Mari gunakan tagar #SenagaruHololiveDay2 di media sosial
Let's use the hashtag #SenagaruHololiveDay2 on social media
saat posting kesamuan mengenai acara ini ya.
when posting about this event.
Karena konser live ini akan menggunakan data berukuran besar,
Since this live concert will use a large amount of data,
kami menyarankan penggunaan Wi-Fi jika Anda menonton dari smartphone.
we recommend using Wi-Fi if you watch from a smartphone.
Jika kualitas koneksi internet Anda tidak memadai,
If your internet connection quality is inadequate,
kami tidak bisa menjanjikan kualitas video,
we cannot promise video quality,
kami mohon pengertiannya.
we ask for your understanding.
Kami berkomitmen untuk mempersiapkan livestream ini dengan sebaik mungkin.
We are committed to preparing this livestream as best as possible.
Namun karena ini merupakan acara yang tayang secara langsung,
However, because this is a live broadcast event,
tetap ada kemungkinan terjadinya masalah teknis.
there remains a possibility of technical issues.
Kami mohon pengertiannya.
We ask for your understanding.
Kami mohon untuk menunggu sebentar sampai pertunjukannya dimulai.
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
本日は「hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ」Day2にご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございますでござる。
Thank you very much for attending Day 2 of "hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiß Schwarz" today!
まもなく開演します！
The concert will begin shortly!
みんな、準備はいいでござるか？
Are you all ready?
せーの、Day2、スタートーー！
Ready, set, Day 2, start!
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
ロボ子さん
Roboco-san
夜空メル
Yozora Mel
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
湊あくあ
Minato Aqua
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
癒月ちょこ
Yuzuki Choco
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
角巻わため
Tsunomaki Watame
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
アユンダ・リス
Ayunda Risu
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Airani Iofifteen
同じ未来を見たいの あの夢手にしたいの
We want to see the same future, and hold that dream in our hands.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れgo
Running with our different hearts, go!
ひらめきに乗って
Riding on a flash of inspiration,
おぼえてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
震えていた 私の声が
My trembling voice...
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day
みんなと掴んだ仲間だよ
Is shared with all of you, my friends.
もっともっともっと加速するハート
Accelerating our hearts more and more and more!
一緒にいくよどこまでも 準備はOK?
Going together anywhere, are you ready?
ひらけ 夢の扉を 1・2・3 きらめきライトアップ
Open the door to dreams, 1, 2, 3, sparkling light up!
同じ未来を見たいの あの夢手にしたいの
We want to see the same future, and hold that dream in our hands.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れgo
Running with our different hearts, go!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
Because you found us right here,
君に会いたく
We wanted to meet you...
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best moments and the best friends,
キラメキに 乗って☆ (イエーイ！)
let's ride on the sparkle! (Yeah!)
覚えているかな 最初の歌 (懐かしいね)
Do you remember? Our first song... (Ah, nostalgia.)
私 声が震えていた (ほんの少し)
My voice was shaking... (Just a little bit.)
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continues from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
is today, which we've grasped together.
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
Speeding up more and more and more and more!
(一緒に) 行くよどこまでも
(Together) We'll go wherever we can!
(are you ready?) 準備は OK？
(Are you ready?) Is your preparation OK?
ひらけ！！ 夢のトビラを (1 2 3) (キラメキ ライダー☆)
Open up the door of dreams! (1, 2, 3) (Sparkling Rider☆)
生まれたての ドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo out!
最高の 時間 最高の 仲間と
With the best moments and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
we're right here because you found us!
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
We wanted to see you, so we came! Let's all sing together!
終わらない メロディ キラメキ に 乗って ☆
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle!☆
届いてるかな 私の声 (はっきりと)
Can you hear it? My voice (ringing clear).
届けたいのは 君に笑顔 (そのスマイル！)
I want to reach you with a smile (that very smile!).
理想の遠さに 悔しくて
Feeling frustrated by how far our ideal is,
みんなと 泣き笑ったね
we cried and laughed together.
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Hold it tight, hold it tight, hold it tight, embrace everything!
(一緒に) 行こう どこまでも
(Together) Let's go wherever we can!
(are you ready?) 準備は OK！
(Are you ready?) Is your preparation OK?!
すすめ！！ 希望の道を (1 2 3) (キラメキ ライダー☆)
Push forward!! The road of hope! (1, 2, 3) (Sparkling Rider☆)
好きな気持ち カラフルに 奏でたいんだ
I want to play my favorite feelings in full color,
最高の場所 最高の みんなと
with the best place and the best everyone!
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
We are here, this is no illusion!
君の心が 幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is painted with happiness,
重ねてく ハーモニー キラメキ 纏って☆
layering our harmonies, intertwined with the sparkle!☆
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing!
そんな願いや わがままでもいいでしょ？
Would such wishes and selfishness be alright?
だって楽しいすぎて！ もっととまらない！！
Because it's too fun! I can't stop anymore!!
輝くステージで もっともっと！！ (お願い) ずっと！！ (オー！ イエーイ！)
On a shining stage, more and more!! (Please) Forever!! (Oh! Yay!)
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
Just saying "happy, fun, and lovable" isn't enough.
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, we still have worries, but...
ここにいるよ 私ここにいるよ
I'm here, I'm right here!
君と同じ世界を見つめて (行くよ？) (キラメキ ライダー☆)
Gazing at the same world as you! (Shall we go?) (Sparkling Rider☆)
生まれたての ドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo out!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best moments and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
we're right here because you found us!
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ みんなで歌おう (せーのっ！)
We wanted to see you, so we came! Let's all sing together! (Ready, set!)
終わらない メロディ キラメキ に 乗って☆ キラメキ 纏って☆ (イエーイ！)
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle!☆ Intertwined with the sparkle!☆ (Yeah!)
2日目も昨日に負けないくらい盛り上がっていくよ！
Even on the second day, I won't lose to yesterday!
幕張！ みんなのコールでより一層盛り上がろう！
Let's go, Makuhari! Let's all go crazy together!
しっかりペンライト振って 一緒に盛り上がろう！
Make sure your penlights are shining, let's get hyped together!
思い通りにいかないことだらけで
There are so many things not going as planned,
どうしようもなく躓きコケを
what can we even do? We keep tripping and falling!
ようようローズの痛みや苦しみから逃げ込める場所を探してる
We search for a place to hide away our tears of pain and regret!
いそいばの隙間に意気込んでも
Throwing ourselves into the gaps of busy days,
月も太陽も無視して眠ろう
even the moon and sun are ignored,
生まれてきたことの意味なんて知らない わかんないよ
I don't even know what being born means, I don't get it!
思い通りにいかないことだらけ
With so many things not going my way,
どうしようもなく自己嫌悪
I feel hopelessly self-loathing.
八百万の痛みや悲しみから
Escaping from countless pains and sorrows,
逃げ込める場所を探している
I'm searching for a place to hide.
いっそ岩の隙間に引きこもって
I might as well hide deep in a rocky crevice,
月も太陽も無視して眠ろう
ignoring the moon and sun to sleep.
生まれてきたことの意味なんて知らない
I don't know the meaning of being born,
分かんないよ
I don't get it at all.
でも そんな風に思えるってこと それは
But the fact that you can think that way—
君がもっともっと素敵になれる力があるって
it tells you that you have the power
教えてるんだよ
to become even more wonderful.
そうさ 神のまにまに 仰せのままに
That's right, at God's mercy, as He commands,
誰だって地球を愛してる
everyone loves the earth.
飲めや歌えや どんちゃん騒ぎ
Drink and sing, make a huge uproar—
たまにはそんなのもいいね
sometimes, that's fine too.
そうさ 北も南も 右も左も
That's right, north and south, right and left,
なんかかんか地球を愛してる
however you look at it, we love the earth.
泥んこだけど歩いて行ける
Muddy though we are, we can keep walking;
まだまだ先は長いさ
we still have a long way to go.
ただ正しい人でいたいだけ
We just want to be righteous people,
きっと誰もがそう願っているけど
surely everyone wishes for that,
八百万の心の醜さに苦しめられる毎日さ
but every day we are tormented by human ugliness.
僕が生まれてきたこと 奇跡と言えば聞こえはいいけど
Me being born—calling it a miracle sounds nice,
それはきっと偶然にすぎなくて やっぱり意味なんてないさ
but it's surely just a coincidence, after all it has no meaning.
でも 例えば君にいじわるをするやつがいるなら
But if there's someone being mean to you,
それは 君がとってもしなやかで素敵なお人だって
it's teaching you that you are a very flexible
教えてるんだよ
and wonderful person.
そうさ 神のまにまに 仰せのままに
That's right, at God's mercy, as He commands,
誰だって地球を愛してる
everyone loves the earth.
僕が笑って君も笑えば許されないことなんてないよ
If I smile and you smile, there's nothing that can't be forgiven.
そうさ 男も女も恋しかるべき
That's right, men and women alike should yearn for love,
そんな風に地球は回ってる
that's how the earth keeps spinning.
泥んこだけど歩いて行こう まだまだ先は長いさ
Muddy though we are, let's keep walking; we still have a long way to go.
うん命なんてないさ
Yes, there's no such thing as fate...
でも 例えば君に意地悪をする奴を
But if there's someone with the breadth of mind
許す度量を持つような奴なら
to forgive a person who is mean to you,
それはそれでとっても素敵な人だって教えてるんだよ
that in itself is a very wonderful person, and it's teaching you that.
そうさ 神のまにまに 仰せのままに 誰だって地球を愛してる
That's right, at God's mercy, as He commands, everyone loves the earth.
僕が笑って君も笑えば許されないことなんてないよ
If I smile and you smile, there's nothing that can't be forgiven.
そうさ 北も南も 右も左も なんかかんか地球を愛してる
That's right, north and south, right and left, however you look at it, we love the earth.
ドロンコだけど歩いていける まだまだ先は長いさ
Muddy though we are, we can keep walking; we still have a long way to go.
本当に大事なものなんて案外くだらないことの中に
Truly important things are surprisingly found within silly things.
あるよ 気づきあえばみんなでバカ騒ぎ 裸踊りして終わらない
They're there. If we notice each other, let's make fools of ourselves and dance naked without end!
そうさ 神のまにまに 仰せのままに もっともっと自分を愛せるよ
That's right, at God's mercy, as He commands, you can love yourself more and more.
鏡を見てごらんよ もう分かったでしょ みんなを照らす光さ
Look into the mirror, you understand now, don't you? You are the light that illuminates everyone.
そうさ 神のまにまに 仰せのままに みんなありがとう やっぱり地球を愛してる
That's right, at God's mercy, as He commands, thank you everyone! After all, we love the earth!
花を咲かせよう 大きな花を 天まで届くくらいの
Let's make flowers bloom, big flowers that reach up to the heavens!
ラララ…
La la la...
はあーっ、ふーっ、ふう…
Haa... fuu...
ホロライブ夏フェス、ディーンク、ユア、ウィッシュ！
Hololive Summer Festival: "Drink Your Wish"!
第1回、いよいよ、始ままりましたー！イエーイ！
The very first one is finally starting! Yay!
皆さん、こんにちはー！こんにちはー！
Hello everyone! Hello!
ホロライブ1期生の…
We're Hololive 1st Generation's...
異世界からやってきたハーフエルフ、アキ・ローゼンタールでーす！イエーイ！
Aki Rosenthal, a half-elf from another world! Yay!
そして、ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアでーす！アローナ！
And I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Gen! Alona!
おかしいの！ここ！ええ、次は…
Wait, that's weird! Okay, next...
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィでーす！アローナ！
And I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive 5th Gen! Alona!
色々なんか、混ざっててよくわからないけれども、
Everything's kind of mixed up and we don't really know what's going on,
私たち、3人で、ホロライブの…ハーフエルフ組です！
but the three of us are Hololive's half-elf group!
ここが違いよ！ホロライブのね、ハーフエルフ組です！
That's the difference! We're Hololive's half-elf group!
ハーフエルフがね、初めて組むユニットで…
It's the very first unit formed by half-elves...
そう、神のまにまにを踊らせていただきましたー！
That's right, we danced to "Kami no Mani Mani"!
イエーイ！みんなどうだった？どうだった？
Yay! How was it, everyone? How was it?
この3人でね、ずっとねやりたかったんだよ。
The three of us have wanted to do this together for so long.
このハーフエルフ組でこの曲を歌いたいと思ってたんですよえー
I've been wanting to sing this song as this half-elf group...
でもかなって本当に良かった！ねえ、すっごく楽しかった！
But I'm so glad it came true! It was so much fun!
楽しかったけど、レッスンもすっごい難しかったよねー
It was fun, but the lessons were super difficult too!
そうだよね、結構なんかステップが浅瀬とか激しかったから、結構心配してたんよね。
Yeah, the steps and stuff were pretty intense, so I was quite worried.
そこはね、本当に、あ、クロズ心配どうもありがとうございます！
Seriously, ah, thanks so much for your worry!
えっってことよ、別に。先輩としてって。
What do you mean "by the way"? As a senior—
だって先輩として当然のことだからさ！
Because as a senior, that's only natural!
なんだそれ。みんなやるじゃん。
What's that? Everyone does it.
いや、ちょっと照れ隠しの時にね、ぜひ使ってて、これ。
No, when you're acting shy, please definitely use this.
えっ使う、じゃあ使う使う。あげるあげる。
Eh, I'll use it then. I'll take it. Here you go.
ということで、ホロライブのね、サーードフェスの2日目いよいよ始まりました！
And with that, Hololive's 3rd Fest Day 2 has finally begun!
昨日も素晴らしいね、ライブステージだったんですけども、2日目のみんなも頑張って練習してきたのでぜひ見守っててください！
Yesterday's live stage was amazing too, but everyone practiced hard for Day 2, so please keep watching over us!
はい！で、みんなはさ、緊張する？
Yes! So, everyone, do you get nervous?
え、緊張します！こんな会場広いんですよ！
Um, I get nervous! Such a huge venue!
あ、そうだよね。私もう泣いちゃったんだ。
Ah, that's right. I already cried.
そうだよ、ちょっとちょっと。もう始まってたよ、すでに。もうんなら歌ったのに。
That's right, wait. It already started. I even sang already.
緊張しすぎて。そうだよ。
Too nervous. That's right.
あ、でもね、そのラミーちゃんのアイドル衣装がね
Ah, but you know, Lamy-chan's idol costume is—
あ、そう、そうなんです！で、ライブで初めてなんじゃないかな
Ah, yes, that's right! And I think it's the first time at a live, right?
そうなんです。ライブでは初めてお披露目になります！
That's right. It's the first time being unveiled at a live!
え、ぜひ見せて見せて！くるくる、かわいいー！
Eh, please show us! Twirl around, so cute!
え、帽子もついてる！かわいい！
Eh, it has a hat too! So cute!
あ、いいね。あ、そうなんです。
Ah, nice. Ah, that's right.
これも雪の結晶が入ってて、本当にここね、アイドルステージで
This also has snow crystals in it, really here, at the idol stage—
アイドルステージ、ライブステージで、うん、もう先輩と一緒にね、ここに立てるってことが本当に嬉しいです！
Being able to stand here on the live stage together with my seniors is truly making me so happy!
もっといろんな人に見せてあげたいね。端っこにもこう見せてあげに行こう。
I want to show it to even more people. Let's go show it to the corners too.
そうだ、こっちの席から二階席のみんな！みんなー！
That's right, from these seats, everyone in the second-floor seats! Everyone!
三階席のみんなもー！いぇーい！見えてるー！いぇーい！
Everyone in the third-floor seats too! Yay! Can you see us? Yay!
次は、次、あ、あそこだ。
Next is, next, ah, over there.
ゴーゴー！二階席のみんなー！やっほー！三階席のみんなー！
Go go! Everyone in the second-floor seats! Hoo-ray! Everyone in the third-floor seats!
いぇーい！あ、だいたい真ん中真ん中！真ん中真ん中！シュッシュッシュッシュッ！
Yay! Ah, about the middle, middle! Middle, middle! Swoosh swoosh swoosh!
それでは、お待たせしました！アリーナ席のみんな！
And now, thanks for waiting! Everyone in the arena seats!
待って待って待って、抜け駆けはやめて。あーらー！
Wait wait wait, don't rush ahead. Oh my!
エロナのみんな！アリーナの皆さんですよ！アリナのみんなー！みんなー！やっほー！
Everyone in Erona! It's everyone in the arena! Arena everyone! Everyone! Hoo-ray!
やっほー！
Hoo-ray!
そしてそして、最後に！
And then, and then, finally!
コメントの！みんなー！見えてるよー！
Everyone in the comments! Everyone! We can see you!
いやあ、楽しいね、これ。
Man, this is fun.
レスポンスとか貰えて、すごく楽しいね。楽しい！はい！
Getting responses and stuff is super fun. Fun! Yes!
でもね、そろそろお時間みたいなの。
But you know, it looks like it's almost time.
うわ、やだ！まだここにいたい！
Whoa, no! I still want to be here!
いたいたいけど、そろそろ怒られそうなのでね。
I want to stay, but we'll probably get scolded soon, so.
はい、次の曲に行きましょうか！
Right, shall we move on to the next song?
ライブはまだまだ前半戦！皆さんこの後もぜひぜひ盛り上げてください！
The live is still in the first half! Everyone, please keep cheering us on after this too!
いぇーい！ありがとうねー！
Yay! Thank you!
はい、せーの、つながるホロライブ！
Ready, set, connecting Hololive!
紫咲シオン
[Murasaki Shion]
百鬼あやめ
[Nakiri Ayame]
暗い方ばっかり見てないで
Don't just keep looking at the dark side
ウラッパッパッパ パラリラ 踊れよ
Urappappappa pararira, dance!
魔界学校の優等生 華やかな我が魔力讃えよ
Honor student of the Demon World, praise our magic!
イナイナイばぁ！でこっち向いて 強く未来を咲かせよ
Look this way with a peekaboo, make the future bloom!
次第相伴して高まって
Gradually coming together, rising higher,
溜まったmp放て黒魔術
unleash accumulated MP with black magic!
定の刻に集え闇に奮えよケルベロス
Gather at the appointed time, tremble, Cerberus!
切に響く言葉はブチギレ発狂パラダイス
Echoing words are a snapping, mad paradise.
キラリ ココロ 奥底 まで 届け
Kirari, reach all the way to the depths of the heart.
これからも 私 の 元 で
From now on, by my side,
不思議 な 力 撃ち放っ て
unleashing mysterious power,
世界 も 笑顔 に なっちゃっ て
making the world smile too!
ウラッパッ パッパ パラ リラ 歌え ば 一生 一緒 だ よね ！？
Sing urappappappa pararira, we'll be together forever, right?!
これからも私の元で 不思議な力打ち放って
From now on by my side, unleashing mysterious power,
世界も笑顔になっちゃって ウラッパッパッパ パラリラ 歌えば
making the world smile too, if we sing urappappappa pararira...
百鬼夜行音頭は上々
The Hyakki Yakou Ondo is top-notch,
今夜は眠れない
And we won't be sleeping tonight!
連日連夜遊び尽くそう
Let's play day and night without end,
満場一致だ da da da da
It's totally unanimous, da da da da!
千万無量溢れてくる
Overflowing with boundless energy,
くすぐる好奇心
Tickling our curiosity.
優柔不断これで決めよう
Let's end indecision right here!
ジャンケンポン
Janken pon!
よっとあいこでしょ
Yotto aiko desho!
ぱーぱー開いた
Opening wide, wide up!
(宵余良い？宵余良い？)
(Is it a good evening? Good evening?)
あっどあっど言わせる
Making everyone gasp in surprise,
花火を打ち上げよう
Let's launch the fireworks up high!
歌え踊れ右にまわれ意気軒昂ピカチの宴
Sing and dance, turn right, a spirited top-tier feast!
さあ騒げ夜に集え可憐な鬼は内
Come on, get wild, gather in the night, cute demons are welcome inside!
歌え踊れ前にならえポンコツそれすら愛嬌
Sing and dance, fall in line, even clumsy quirks are charming!
さあ騒げ暁まで可憐な鬼は内
Come on, get wild till dawn, cute demons are welcome inside!
ああ千客来来晃々大饗宴を
Ah, thousands of guests arriving in brilliant splendor,
さらう音に乗せられて
Carried away by the sweeping music,
なんてったって盛大派手に行き踊った
No matter what, let's dance grandly and flashily!
天真爛漫 宵の余、良い！
Innocent and carefree, what a good evening!
余だぞ～こっからはもっともっと盛り上げるために
It's Yo! From here on, to hype things up even more,
みんなに合いの手をしてもらおうと思う
I want everyone to give me your call and response!
余っ余っ余良いの宵の余良い
Yott' yott' yoi no yoi no yoi yoi!
せっせっせーのよいよいよい 振り乱す
Sesse sse- no yoi yoi yoi, swinging away,
せっせっせーのよいいよいで 現世を埋め尽くそう
Let's fill up and bury the mortal world!
明鏡止水目を瞑って
Closing my eyes like clear water and still mirrors,
ひと息入れちまって
Taking a brief moment to catch my breath,
美味甘味味わったら
Once I taste something sweet and delicious,
感涙必至だ da da da da
Tears of emotion are guaranteed, da da da da!
永永無窮終わりたくない
Eternal and infinite, I never want it to end!
何して遊ぼうか
What should we play next?
暗中模索これで決めよう
Groping in the dark, let's decide with this!
ジャンケンポン
Janken pon!
よっとあいこでしょ
Yotto aiko desho!
ぐーっとぐーっとこらえて
Holding back tightly, guu-tto guu-tto,
わーっとわーっと湧くほど
Until it swells up, waa-tto waa-tto,
太鼓を打ち鳴らそう
Let's beat and echo the taiko drums!
泣いて笑え余に続けキラキラのキンピカ掲げ
Cry and laugh, follow Yo, raising sparkling golden lights!
さあおいで拒みはせぬ可憐な鬼は内
Come on, no refusals allowed, cute demons are welcome inside!
泣いて笑え前に進め期待値高めで良いぞ
Cry and laugh, press forward, high expectations are fine!
きらびやかな今度は徐々今夜は眠れない
Sparkling brightly now, slowly we won't sleep tonight!
連日連夜遊び尽くそう
Let's play day and night without end,
満場一致だ da da da da
It's totally unanimous, da da da da!
千万無量溢れてくる
Overflowing with boundless energy,
くすぐる好奇心
Tickling our curiosity.
優柔不断これで決めよう
Let's end indecision right here!
ジャンケンポン
Janken pon!
よっとあいこでしょ
Yotto aiko desho!
ぱーぱー開いた
Opening wide, wide up!
あっとあっと思い出させる花火を打ち上げよう
Making everyone gasp in surprise with fireworks!
歌え踊れ右にまわれ意気軒昂ピカチの宴
Sing and dance, turn right, a spirited top-tier feast!
さあ騒げ夜に集え可憐な鬼は内
Come on, get wild, gather in the night, cute demons are welcome inside!
歌え踊れ前にならえポンコツそれすら愛嬌
Sing and dance, fall in line, even clumsy quirks are charming!
さあ騒げ暁まで可憐な鬼は内
Come on, get wild till dawn, cute demons are welcome inside!
ああ千客来来晃々大饗宴を
Ah, thousands of guests arriving in brilliant splendor,
さらう音に乗せられて
Carried away by the sweeping music,
なんてったって盛大派手に行き踊った
No matter what, let's dance grandly and flashily!
天真爛漫 宵の余、良い！
Innocent and carefree, what a good evening!
明鏡止水目を瞑って
Closing my eyes like clear water and still mirrors,
ひと息入れちまって
Taking a brief moment to catch my breath,
美味甘味味わったら
Once I taste something sweet and delicious,
感涙必至だ da da da da
Tears of emotion are guaranteed, da da da da!
永永無窮終わりたくない
Eternal and infinite, I never want it to end!
何して遊ぼうか
What should we play next?
暗中模索これで決めよう
Groping in the dark, let's decide with this!
ジャンケンポン
Janken pon!
よっとあいこでしょ
Yotto aiko desho!
ぐーっとぐーっとこらえて
Holding back tightly, guu-tto guu-tto,
わーっとわーっと湧くほど
Until it swells up, waa-tto waa-tto,
太鼓を打ち鳴らそう
Let's beat and echo the taiko drums!
泣いて笑え余に続けキラキラのキンピカ掲げ
Cry and laugh, follow Yo, raising sparkling golden lights,
さあおいで拒みはせぬ可憐な鬼は内
Come on, no refusals allowed, cute demons are welcome inside!
泣いて笑え前に進め期待値高めで良いぞ
Cry and laugh, press forward, high expectations are fine!
さあおいで遠縁無用可憐な鬼は内
Come on, put aside all reserve, cute demons are welcome inside!
ああ抱腹絶倒騒々夜を飾る
Ah, side-splitting laughter decorates the bustling night,
眩しい声に連れられて
Drawn in by the dazzling voices,
なんてったって最終派手にまたでんしんだまいよのよよい
No matter what, let's go all out flashy till the very end!
天真爛漫 宵の余、良い！
Innocent and carefree, what a good evening!
夜だぞ～
It's night time!
今日は3度目す! もっともっと盛り上げるためにみんなに合いの手して貰うよ!
This is the third time! To hype it up even more, I'm asking everyone for your call and response!
夜についてきてね!
Follow along into the night!
いくぞー！せーの！よっよっよっよ！
Let's go! Ready, set! Yo, yo, yo, yo!
よい よい よい よい
Yoi yoi yoi yoi!
せい せい せい の よい よい よい 繰り出す
Unleashing a festive yoi yoi yoi!
せい せい せい の よい よい よい 人生を埋め尽くそう
Let's fill up our lives with yoi yoi yoi!
歌え踊れ右回り 冴え渡る今宵は
Sing and dance, spinning right, tonight is crystal clear
さあ騒げ一夜限りの青空には
Come make some noise, in tonight's one-night-only blue sky
歌え踊れ舞い倣え 迷走僕こそ愛嬌
Sing and dance, follow along, wandering, I'm the charming one
さあ騒げ飽きるまで 枯れ果てんなお似合いさ
Come make some noise until you're sick of it, don't wither up, it suits you
手繰りもぐりこんだ
Pulled and diving in, carried along by fate
なぜだか切ない 派手にはしゃいで精神乱舞
For some reason it's bittersweet, wild spirit dance
ばばばば
Ba-ba-ba-ba!
大神ミオ 兎田ぺこら 角巻わため 獅白ぼたん
Ookami Mio / Usada Pekora / Tsunomaki Watame / Shishiro Botan
明日の天気だとか 流行りのものも全部
Tomorrow's weather, and all the trendy things
あなたが今知りたいこと あたしがみーんな教えるから
Everything you want to know right now, I'll teach you all of it!
でもあなたは何を知りたいのか あたしはわからないんだよ
But what is it you want to know? I don't know that...
算命学でも星占いでもタロット占いでも あたしたちの相性最悪だけど
In numerology, astrology, or tarot, our compatibility is the worst
どうぶつ占いならあたしたちは 相性抜群のカップルだって ねえ こっち向いてよ
With animal divination, we're a perfect couple! Hey, look here!
でもあなたは何を知りたいのか あたしはわからないんだよ
But what is it you want to know? I don't know that...
算命学でも風水術でも手相占いでも
Numerology, feng shui, palmistry... our...
動物占いならあたしたちは 相性抜群のカップルだって
Even with the worst compatibility, animal divination makes us a match!
占いによると あなたの悩みごとは
According to the divination, your worries...
あたしにすべて話すことで
By telling everything to me...
身体ごとわき消えるのです
Will disappear entirely from your body...
でもあなたは何を悩んでいるのか あたしはわからないんだよ
But what is it you're worried about? I don't know that...
惨憺たるだけども あなたの知らないところなら
Even if it's tragic, if it's somewhere you don't know...
なんだったって知ってるよ ねえ 伝えさせてよ
I know all about it! Hey, let me tell you!
あなたは黒表で黙っていたって いいところならなんだって知ってるよ
Even if you stayed silent like a black panther, I know it all!
あしたの天気だとか
What the weather will be tomorrow,
流行りのものも全部
or what's in fashion, everything
あなたが今知りたいこと
that you want to know right now,
あたしがみーんな教えてあげるから
I'll teach you all of it, so...
でもあなたが何を知りたいのか
But what is it you want to know?
あたしはわからないんだよ
That, I don't really know...
あなたの視線を奪い続けてる
continuing to steal your gaze,
あの娘がいつもロマンチックだったのが
that that girl was always so romantic
ちょっと悔しかったんだ
made me a little envious.
算命学でも星占いででも
In predictions, in astrology,
タロット占いでも
or in tarot divinations,
あたしたちの相性最悪だけど
we seem to find we're the worst match, but
どうぶつ占いならあたしたちは
if we use animal divination,
相性抜群のカップルだって
we could be a perfectly compatible couple,
ねぇ、こっち向いてよ
so hey, look at me.
動物占いなんて頼らなくたって
Even without depending on animal divination,
あたしがあなたの好みに変わるから
I could change to your preferences,
ねぇ、こっち向いてよ
so hey, look at me.
DAY2 無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of DAY2 has ended. Thank you for watching!
DAY2 free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
DAY2 無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of DAY 2 has ended. Thank you for watching!